saregama.com 2019-06-30

# Evergreen Hindi Songs, Ghazals & Devotional music from Saregama

## Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy governs the use of www.saregama.com, owned and controlled by Saregama India Limited ("Saregama") and shall be read with the Terms Of Use.

At Saregama we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

### What this policy covers

This policy covers how Saregama treats personal information that we collect and receive, including information related to your past use of Saregama products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Saregama does not own or control, or to people that Saregama does not employ or manage.

### Information collection and use

**GENERAL**

Saregama may collect personal information when you register with Saregama, when you use Saregama products or services, when you visit Saregama pages or the pages of certain Saregama business partners. Saregama may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.

When you register Saregama may ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, PIN/ZIP code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. For some products and services Saregama might also ask for your address, address proof document, PAN number, and information about your assets. When you register with Saregama and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.

Saregama may use information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, communicate offers, promotion and marketing of Saregama/ our Business Partner's services, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. 

### Information Sharing and disclosure

Saregama does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with Saregama under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help Saregama communicate with you about offers from Saregama and our business partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.

We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Saregama terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

We transfer information about you if Saregama is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Saregama will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. Saregama does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad.

Your Ability to Edit Your Account Information and Preferences

You can edit your Saregama Account information including your preferences at any time.

New categories of marketing communications might be added to the Marketing Preferences page from time to time. Users who visit this page can opt out of receiving future marketing communications from these new categories or they can unsubscribe by following instructions contained in the messages they receive. Unless unsubscribed by you, Saregama reserves the right to contact you through voice, Short Messaging Service, text, e-mail, post, on/ through social networking sites etc. for any of the purposes mentioned herein.

We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the Saregama service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the Saregama Newsletter(s), that are considered part of your Saregama account.

### Confidentiality and Security

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.

We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect personal information about you. However, Saregama cannot be held liable for any disclosure/ damage/ loss or any other consequence of a security breach whether by way of any virus/ trojan/ worm/ malicious software or otherwise affecting your private or public data.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

Saregama may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Saregama account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

### Questions or suggestions:

If you have any comments, questions or suggestions, please complete a feedback form or you can contact us at:

**E-mail :** [ feedback@saregama.com ](mailto:feedback@saregama.com)  
Saregama India Limited  
# 33 Jessore Road  
Dum Dum  
Kolkata 700028  
Effective from 15th March 2007
